<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ce-deploy</title>
    <link>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ce-deploy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/_sidebar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/_sidebar/</guid>
      <description>   Home   Install   Usage   Roles   Config   Drupal 8   Matomo   Drupal 8   Opcache     ce-dev   ce-dev prebuild     CLI Tools   Drush   Drush     Composer   Config   Drupal 8   Drupal 8   Mautic     Cron   Database backup cron task   Database backup cron task - MySQL     Database backup cron task - MySQL   Mautic cron tasks     Data backups   MySQL backups     Deploy   &amp;ldquo;Meta&amp;rdquo;   Drupal 8   Matomo   Mautic     Sync roles   Database sync   Database sync - MySQL           </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/contribute/</guid>
      <description>Contribute Documentation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/install/</guid>
      <description>Install The stack only gets tested on Debian Buster, but should run on any Linux distribution, as long as Ansible &amp;gt;=2.9 is present. You can install either:
 through ce-provision  manually by running a local playbook with Docker (soon)  Install with ce-provision The companion ce-provision stack already provides an &amp;ldquo;ce_deploy&amp;rdquo; role you can add to your playbooks. This is the recommended way if you use ce-provision already.
Install manually Dependencies The main prerequesites are obviously Ansible and git.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/readme/</guid>
      <description>ce-deploy A set of Ansible roles and wrapper scripts to deploy (web) applications.
Overview The &amp;ldquo;stack&amp;rdquo; from this repo is to be installed on a &amp;ldquo;deploy&amp;rdquo; server/runner, to be used in conjonction with a CI/CD tool (Jenkins, Gitlab, Travis, &amp;hellip;). It allows the deploy steps for a given app to be easily customizable at will, and to be stored alongside the codebase of the project. When triggered from a deployment tool, the stack will clone the codebase and &amp;ldquo;play&amp;rdquo; a given deploy playbook from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/roles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/roles/</guid>
      <description>Roles Ansible roles and group of roles that constitute the deploy stack.
Sync roles  Roles that sync data/assets between environments.
Database sync  Roles that sync databases between environments.
&amp;ldquo;Meta&amp;rdquo;  Roles that bundles other individual roles together for tackling common use cases.
Drupal 8  Role for deploying single Drupal 8 instances, or multisites with a single database.
Data backups  Generate backups for each build.
MySQL backups  Generate MySQL backups for each build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codeenigma.github.io/ce-deploy-docs/1.x/scripts/</guid>
      <description>Usage While you can re-use/fork roles or call playbooks directly from your deployment tool, it is recommended to use the provided wrapper scripts, as they will take care of setting up the needed environments.
Deploy with the &amp;ldquo;build&amp;rdquo; script In the script folder, you&amp;rsquo;ll see a build.sh script. This is the easiest/safest way to trigger deployments, as it bundles all the steps in one.
Arguments You will need to pass at least the following information:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>